[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What other name is commonly used to refer to sweet and sour sauce in China?", "correct_answer": "The peoples sauce", "incorrect_answers": ["The red delight", "The two opposites in one", "Woman and man sauce"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On which of the Philippine islands is the active Taal Volcano located?", "correct_answer": "Luzon", "incorrect_answers": ["Mindanao", "Visayas", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is NOT located in the country of Madagascar?", "correct_answer": "Bodrum", "incorrect_answers": ["Nosy-Be", "Antananarivo", "Antsirabe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The consumption of raw pineapple is contraindicated for people who suffer from this disease.", "correct_answer": "Liver disease", "incorrect_answers": ["Heart disease", "Diabetes", "AIDS"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where did Samantha Baker and her family live in the film Sixteen Candles?", "correct_answer": "Illinois", "incorrect_answers": ["New York", "Detroit", "Philadelphia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many are in a Bakers Dozen?", "correct_answer": "13", "incorrect_answers": ["10", "12", "5"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Are beagles easy to housebreak?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the end of the movie Mean Girls, Cady ended up with Aaron Samuels.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of cells are the Purkinje cells, named after Czech anatomist Jan Evangelista Purkyne?", "correct_answer": "Neurons", "incorrect_answers": ["Epithelial cells", "Osteoblasts", "Smooth muscle cells"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If a cat pushes its face against your head, this means what?", "correct_answer": "Acceptance", "incorrect_answers": ["Impatience", "Submission", "Aggression"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Although only a small percent of scorpions are venomous to people, 800 to 2000 human deaths each year are caused by scorpions. During which part of the day are these creatures most active?", "correct_answer": "Night", "incorrect_answers": ["Morning", "All day", "Noon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Diamond Tree, a giant Karri tree located south of Manjimup, Western Australia, has been of practical use to the natives since 1939, serving as what?", "correct_answer": "Fire look-out platform", "incorrect_answers": ["Accommodation for native homeless", "Military watch tower", "Warehouse"]}]